// Storing questions and answers for the quiz
// Code inspired by: How To Make Quiz Website Using HTML CSS And Javascript
// Source: Codehal
// URL: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vp8x8-reqZA

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "In which movie does a young girl named Satsuki and her sister Mei move to the countryside and discover magical creatures?",
        answer: "My Neighbor Totoro",
        options: [
            "Spirited Away",
            "My Neighbor Totoro",
            "Ponyo",
            "Howl's Moving Castle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The film 'Kiki's Delivery Service' is set in a fictional European city and follows a young witch who starts a delivery business.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the primary setting of the film 'Castle in the Sky'?",
        answer: "A floating island called Laputa",
        options: [
            "A floating island called Laputa",
            "A bustling metropolis",
            "A magical forest",
            "An underwater kingdom"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which movie features this robot statue?",
        image: "assets/images/question-images/quiz-img-q4-robot.webp",
        answer: "Castle in the Sky",
        options: [
            "Castle in the Sky",
            "The Secret World of Arrietty",
            "The Cat Returns",
            "Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In 'Princess Mononoke,' who is the leader of the boar tribe?",
        answer: "Okkoto",
        options: [
            "San",
            "Jigo",
            "Ashitaka",
            "Okkoto"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The protagonist of 'The Wind Rises,' Jiro Horikoshi, is based on a real historical figure.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the main conflict in the film 'Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind'?",
        answer: "A battle between humans and giant insects",
        options: [
            "A battle between humans and giant insects",
            "A war over magical artefacts",
            "The struggle to save a dying princess",
            "A quest to find a lost kingdom"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the name of this character?",
        image: "assets/images/question-images/quiz-img-q8-baron.webp",
        answer: "Baron",
        options: [
            "Baron",
            "Muta",
            "Jiji",
            "Luna"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "In 'Whisper of the Heart,' what is the name of the antique shop that plays a significant role in the film?",
        answer: "The Baron's Shop",
        options: [
            "The Cat's Store", 
            "The Antique Shop of Dreams",
            "The Baron's Shop", 
            "The Moonlight Shop"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "'The Tale of the Princess Kaguya' was created using CGI animation.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    }
];